tutsbuzz.com 2013-05-17

# 3D, Photoshop and Programming Tutorials | TutsBuzz.com

We here at Tutsbuzz.com greatly respect your privacy and we hope that our users feel that the information they share with us is 100% secure and private. Here are the guidelines we follow at Tutsbuzz to ensure your privacy and our integrity: 

###  Registration 

In order to use this website to the full potential, we highly recommend you to first complete the registration form. In this way you can associate your username with the tutorial you posted. During registration a user is required to give their e-mail address, nickname, and other optional identifiers. This information is to identify the user, and for other users to interact with the user. None of this information will be sold, transmitted, or in any other way sent to any third parties. 

###  Session 

Sessions are used to identify the user when he/she logs in. A session is a piece of data stored on the server's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a session is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the session simply terminates. More specifically, we use this on Tutsbuzz.com in that the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. 

###  Passwords 

Passwords will never be asked by Tutsbuzz staff. If someone does ask for your password or other info, please immediately notify us. 

###  Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tutsbuzz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

###  Conclusion 

Tutsbuzz.com will never, under any circumstances give away or displays your IP address. Additionally, Tutsbuzz.com will never sell or transmit e-mail addresses or any other personal identifiers to 3rd parties. Use of the registration system is optional; however it does maximize the user's experience here at the site. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to [Contact Us](http://www.tutsbuzz.com/contact.html)! Thank you for your cooperation.
